educationobserver.com 2015-05-31

# Privacy Policy www.educationobserver.com

### Privacy Policy www.educationobserver.com 

**What information do we collect?**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or sending a contact request. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements .

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your visits to our website

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website and/or other sites on the Internet. . 

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Website advertisers other than Google also places their advertisements and tracking cookies on this website, You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website  
](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**   
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.educationobserver.com/disclaimer>

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.educationobserver.com  
Konneckal, Manathmangalam  
Perinthalmanna, Kerala 679322  
India  
biju(at)netri(dot)co(dot)in
